<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Bianca&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Bianca&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:40:24 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Finding the Perfect Gluten-Free Chocolate Chip Cookie</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:40:24 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cookies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The best part of Christmas at my family&amp;rsquo;s house is the cookies. Each year, my family cranks out dozens of homemade cookies for a Christmas party, and then more for Christmas Day (because there are never enough left after the party).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I was diagnosed with celiac disease in March 2023, when December rolled around, I was sad that my favorite tradition was never going to be the same. Making those family recipes gluten-free, while feasible, never had the same texture or taste. While certain cookies have improved over the years (Andes mint chip cookie recipe - the key was reducing the flour 10%), others remain difficult to convert to a GF version. Here&amp;rsquo;s what last year&amp;rsquo;s cookie tray looked like:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Park Adventures</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/nationalparks2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 16:42:20 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/nationalparks2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In 2025, I&amp;rsquo;ve been to nine national parks, and each of them has been a life-changing experience. In January, we snowshoed in Glacier NP while skiing in Whitefish, MT. In March, my friends and I drove up from LA to Yosemite National Park. In July and August, I spent over three weeks driving around the Rocky Mountains from Austin, Texas all the way up to Yellowstone in Wyoming. Here&amp;rsquo;s my recap, through data and photos!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Devastating Effects of Illegal Mining in North Brazil</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/mining/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 17:50:47 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/mining/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure width=&#34;50%&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/garimpo.jpg&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;Yanomami in Brazil call for an end to mining in their lands. Image by Victor Moriyama/ISA.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During the four years of Jair Bolsonaro’s presidency, 570 children in the Yanomami territory were killed by disease and malnutrition (Machado et al.). The relatively isolated Indigenous tribe in Northwest Brazil has been victim to the quick expansion of illegal mining in the country. The arrival of &lt;em&gt;garimpeiros&lt;/em&gt; (Portuguese term for miners who work in the small-scale gold mining camps) has caused mercury poisoning, the spread of diseases, and the destruction of Yanomami homes and food supplies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
